Design and evaluation of a prototype of augmented reality applied to
medical devices
-"Even though use of medical devices is extremely beneficial for patient care, potential problems associated with their use may produce
severe, negative consequences, compromising patient safety."

-"medical device manufacturers
are obliged by Spanish legislation for each device to include “the necessary information to use it completely safely and properly, considering potential users’ training and knowledge, and to identify the
manufacturer”"

-"Participation from the research team, as future users, led to
a participatory design involving users in the design of the device [22].
"

General Requirements for Industrial Augmented Reality Applications
-" Although Augmented Reality applications have been used
successfully in medical or military contexts for many years, industrial applications are often perceived as isolated solutions that are only applicable
in a defined and static work environment."

-" Although the integration of individual workpieces is a strongly desired feature, it requires considerable development effort, which leads to additional
costs and cannot be performed instantly."

Pottential applications for virtual and augmented reality technologies in sensory science
-". Increasingly, sensory data techniques are moving towards
more dynamic aspects of sensory perception, taking account of the various stages of user-product interactions.
Recent technological advancements in virtual reality and augmented reality have unlocked the potential for new
immersive and interactive systems which could be applied as powerful tools for capturing and deciphering the
complexities of human sensory perception."

-"Augmented reality is a relatively newer form of human-computer interaction which superimposes computer-generated information into a
person's view of the real world, creating an illusion where both virtual and real objects coexist in the same space (Ong & Nee, 2004)"

-"Therefore, AR can be differentiated from VR, given that the former overlays
digital information in a real environment, rather than completely replacing it. In addition to combining real and virtual information, a true
AR system should run interactively in real time, and seamlessly align
natural world and virtual objects with each other (Azuma et al., 2001;
Kipper & Rampolia, 2013)."

-"The earliest technological development in AR can be traced back to Ivan Sutherland's work on the Swords of Damocles HMD."

-"recreating a physical
immersive environment could improve the ecological validity of research, it requires a relatively large amount of space and can be a rather
expensive and time-consuming task."

-"However, regardless of the approach, it must be kept
in mind that research on the contextual effects VR/AR environments is
in its infancy, and further research is necessary to facilitate their confident application in improving the reliability of consumer sensory
evaluations."

-"therefore the accuracy of
the data is dependent on the individual's ability to articulate their hedonic and emotional perceptions to food stimuli."

-"VR and AR can also enable the interactive visualisation of complex food ingredient structures and their interplay with dynamic sensory data, enhancing our understanding of oral food processing, potentially leading to new manufacturing practices, food products and
customer experiences"

Towards augmented reality manuals for industry 4.0: A methodology.
-"These innovations in ICT (Information and Communication Technologies) and computer sciences a?ect also industrial manufacturing. Started in Germany, this trend is called the 4th Industrial Revolution, in shorthand, Industry 4.0 [1]."

Potentials of Augmented Reality in Training 
-"The debate surrounding about changing processes by using new technologies, this also implies a change in the way people work."
-"This raises the question of how far digital supporting systems, in particular AR technologies, not only improve the process itself, but can also be used as an innovative medium for practice-oriented learning."

Augmented reality in support of Industry 4.0—Implementation challenges and success factors
-"AR is an important technology for the Industry4.0 approach[2]. As those approaches promote a human-centric industrial environment, AR is one approach to augment the worker[12]."
-"AR is a complex technology.Thiscomplexity arises on the one hand from the technology itself. The system has to be integrated into the current IT infrastructure"
-"The availability of innovative computer graphics interfaces, like Augmented and Virtual Reality, can change signiﬁcantly the way technicalinformationispresentedtotheuser"
-"In the industrial ﬁeld, AR or VR contents have been proposed as a support for maintenance [22,37], for assembly simulation [38–41] sometimes including tactile communication and also to improve information delivery and 
perception in manufacturing systems [42]. Furthermore VR has also been proposed as a tool to support industrial processes, for example to improve processes control [43], 
to analyze and improve ergonomics [44] or to study and analyze human-robot interaction [45]."
-" In AR manuals it is important to provide only the needed information without useless details because they imply the use of text that occludes the real scene and is diﬃcult to relate unambiguously with the rest of instruction provided with visual elements."

Design Considerations for combining Augmented Reality with intelligent tutors.
-"A simple Google scholar search on “Intelligent Tutoring Systems” returns more than 57,000 results, whereas search on “Intelligent Tutoring Systems and Augmented Reality” returns a mere 57 results."
-"AR is a subset of “mixed reality”, the blending of physical and virtual worlds (Fig. 2) [21]."

Design Considerations for combining Augmented Reality with intelligent tutors.
-"The Virtual and Augmented Reality Design System (VADS) is a training system that uses both AR and VR to help mechanical engineers develop their own problem solving and mechanical ability using a personalised learning approach."

Mobile Augmented Reality: the potential for education
-"Due to the rising popularity of mobile devices globally, the widespread use of AR on mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets has become a growing phenomenon. "
-"The transformation of teaching and learning caused by technology has certainly provides an exciting opportunities to design learning environment that are realistic, authentic, engaging and extremely fun."

Perspectives on how to evaluate augmented reality technology tools for education: a systematic review
-".The coexistence of virtual and real environments allows learners to experience phenomena that otherwise would be impossible in the real world.This allows learners to visualize complex spatial relationships and abstract concepts and,therefore,develop important abilities that cannot be evolved in other technology learning environments[78]."

Supporting remote maintenance in industry 4.0 through augmented reality 
-" the maintenance expert should be able to see why and where the failure occurred, to understand how to perform the maintenance activity"

A MOBILE APPLICATION OF AUGMENTED REALITY FOR AEROSPACE MAINTENANCE TRAINING
-""

Retargeting Technical Documentation to Augmented Reality
-""